GRIGORI ARAMYAN

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER



Profile

Born in 1991, Yerevan, Armenia. Have engineering and technical background. Trained Android developer and self-taught Web Full-Stack Engineer. Passion for learning new things and growing with little steps every day. Experienced in PHP/Laravel, Python/Django, Elixir/Phoenix, Node js, React js, Vue js, Twig, HTML, CSS preprocessors, build tools. Perseverant.

Experience

2015 - 2015 EatFully (UK startup)
 Android developer
2016 - 2016 SKU Market (Russian startup)
 Full-Stack Web Engineer
2016 - 2017 Innovities (Armenian startup)
 Full-Stack Web Engineer
2017 - 2018 Chit Learning (Armenian startup)
 Full-Stack Web Engineer
2018 - Present ArmCoding
 Full-Stack Web Engineer

Education

2008 - 2012 Industrial electronics
 SEUA, Yerevan
2014 - 2014 Android development course
 ACA, Yerevan

Interests

Robotics

Robotics and IoT system construction

Music

Music for high vibrations of the mind

Poetry

For getting into different worlds

Hiking

Passion for hiking and mountaineering

Contact

- ★ Yerevan
- **** +374 94 535279
- grigori.aramyan@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/grig ori-aramyan-88437b12a/
- f https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100006445180574